pokerlistings.com 2003-12-03

# Pokerlistings.com - Find the best online poker

|   
---  
  
|  |  | Online  
poker rooms |  | Software |  | Poker  
supplies |  | News  
& Content |  | Strategy  
& Rules |  | Game  
specific |  | Forums |  | Directories |  | Int'l  
sites |  | Tournaments |  | All  
Categories » |   
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
|  | **Search:** |  |  |  |  |  |  Bookmark Pokerlistings »  
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
|   
---  
|  Home > **Privacy policy** |  |  |   
  
| Privacy policy  |   
---|---|---  
|   
---  
|  PokerListings.com respects your privacy. All information collected at this website will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, loaned, or otherwise disclosed. Any information you give to Pokerlistings.com will be held with the uttermost care, and will not be used in ways that you have not consented to. 

1\. Resale or disclosure of information to third parties:  
Pokerlistings.com does not sell, rent, trade, loan, or lease any personal information collected at our site, including membership forms or email lists. 

2\. Browser information collected on the website:  
PokerListings.com analyses the website logs to improve the value of the materials available on website. Our website logs are not personally identifiable, and we make no attempt to link them with the individuals that actually browse the site. 

3\. Advertisements:  
We currently have ads served by an in-house program, which follow those privacy guidelines. 

4\. Use of cookies:  
PokerListings.com does use cookies on its website, mostly in order to track traffic coming from other websites and leaving to other websites. With the cookies, we make no attempt to link them with the individuals to make any information personally identifiable. 

5\. Updates and changes:  
PokerListings.com reserves the right to replace this "privacy policy" at any time. We suggest that you regularly check: [http://www.pokerlistings.com/index/info/privacy_policy/]()

Please email: [info@pokerlistings.com](mailto:info@pokerlistings.com) with questions or comments. 

|   
|   
Advertise | Contact us | Add your site | [Suggestions to make us better](mailto:webmaster@pokerlistings.com) | Tell a friend   
   
PokerListings.com is an independent online poker information website, not affiliated with any poker room.  
Copyright © 2003 Pokerlistings.com - All Rights Reserved.  
PokerListings.com is managed and operated by Result Venture K. I. Inc. Company.  
Please read our Privacy Policy and Disclaimer

PokerListings.com the online poker guide and directory provides information on online poker, best poker games, best poker sites, best poker rooms, best poker promotions, best poker bonus, free online poker, poker strategies, how to play poker online, poker hands, official poker rules, top poker download, top poker software, winning poker strategy, texas holdem, Omaha, world series of poker, poker hands, poker chips, poker table, poker game, download poker, play poker online, poker room, poker links, internet poker, and multi player poker. Yes – we have it all!
